Rider?
ライダー
Idiot!
馬鹿
What's wrong with you, breaking the shutter open like that?
シャッター蹴破って出てくるなんて何考えてんだ
なんで入るときみたいに霊体化しないんだよ
Why didn't you take spirit form, like when you went in?!
I can't carry these in spirit form.
霊体のままでは　これを持って歩けんではないか
Stop panicking.
そう狼狽えるでない
You make me sound like a thief.
まるで盗人か何かのようではないか
If you're not a thief, then what are you?!
盗人じゃなくて何なんだよ　お前
There's a big difference.
大いに違う　闇に紛れて逃げ去るのなら匹夫の夜盗
A cowardly thief would sneak away in the night.
The King of Conquerors sings triumphantly as he leaves with his loot!
凱歌とともに立ち去るのならば　それは征服王の略奪だ
I'll carry these!
これでいいだろ　さあ消えろ　いま消えろ　すぐ消えろ
Now disappear. Disappear right now!
Very well! I shall leave you to carry the spoils.
おお　では荷運びは任せた　くれぐれも落とすなよ
Be careful not to drop them.
ああもう　どうしてこうなるんだよ
Geez! Why is this happening to me?!
Utw
Presents
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
The summoning went fine, so why is this happening?
召喚に成功したってのに
何で僕がこんな目に
World Map
World Now!
See the
And what's the deal with these books, anyway?
大体何なんだよう　この本は
World Map
World Now!
I told you. They're preparations for the war.
戦の準備をすると言っただろう
War cannot be waged without maps.
戦に地図は必要不可欠だからな
Hey, boy.
おい　坊主　マケドニアとペルシャはどこだ
Where are Macedonia and Persia?
Wh-What's with that attitude?!
何だ　その態度は　僕はお前のマス
I'm your Ma...
I'm well aware that you are my Master.
貴様が余のマスターだということくらい分かっておるわ
Did we not forge a contract?
ちゃんと契約も交わしたではないか
Yeah.
I'm more interested in learning where the territories I ruled over are.
それより　かつての余の領土はどこかと聞いておるのだ
Around here, I guess.
この辺かな
Tiny! I spent my life conquering
that land, and behold how tiny it is!
小さい　あれだけ駆け回った大地がこの程度か
良い良い　胸が高鳴る
Very well! I cannot wait!
Where are we now on the map, boy?
では坊主　今我々がいるのはこの地図のどこなのだ
Here.
ここだよ
Right on the other side of the world, then.
丸い大地の反対側か
Pleasing news yet again!
これまた痛快
This will guide us in the coming battles.
これで戦の指針も固まったな
Guide us?
指針って
まずは世界を半周する
First, we head to the other side of the world.
We go west, and only west.
西へ　ひたすら西へ
And we shall conquer every land we pass through!
通りがかった国はすべて陥としていく
I shall return to Macedonia triumphantly,
そうやってマケドニアへ凱旋し  故国の皆に余の復活を祝賀させる
and my people will hold a festival to honor my revival.
Exciting, is it not?
心躍るであろう
Do you even know what you're here for?!
お前　何しに来たんだよ　聖杯戦争だろう　聖杯
You're here for the Grail War! The Grail!
That's right.
そうだ　聖杯といえば　最初に問っておくべきだった
Speaking of the Grail, I forgot to ask...
What will you do with the Grail, boy?
坊主　貴様はどう聖杯を使う
Wh-Why would you want to know?
何だよ改まって　そんなこと訊いてどうする
Why would you care?
World Map
If you are also intent on conquering the world,
もし貴様もまた世界を獲る気なら 即ち余の仇敵ではないか
World Map
that would make you my enemy.
The world cannot serve two lords.
覇王は二人といらんからな
World conquest?
世界征服なんて
I-I'll tell you what I want.
僕が望むのはな
I just want people to treat me fairly.
ひとえに正当な評価だけだ
The people at the Clock Tower don't acknowledge my talents, and I want to change that!
ついぞ僕の才能を認めなかった時計塔の連中に  考えを改めさせることだ
小さいわ
Small!
Small! And so narrow-minded!
小さい
狭い
阿呆らしい
How foolish.
You're in this battle just for your reputation?
戦いに賭ける大望が おのれの沽券を示すことのみだと
And you dare call yourself my Master?!
貴様それでも余のマスターか
How disappointing!
まったくもって嘆かわしい
If you wish so desperately for others to revere you...
そうまでして　他人に畏敬されたいというのなら
perhaps you should use the Grail's power to grow another thirty centimeters.
貴様はまず聖杯の力であと三十センチほど背丈を伸ばしてもらえ
How dare he talk to me like that?! He's just my Servant!
この　たかがサーヴァントの分際で
I'll show him!
おもい知らせてやる
I address my Command Spell.
令呪に告げる　聖杯の規律に従い
Abiding by the Grail's laws, I order Iskandar, King of Conquerors...
この者　征服王イスカンダルに
Calm down, Waver.
落ち着け　ウェイバー
マスターが与えられた令呪で
A Master can use his Command Spells to compel his Servant's obedience only three times.
サーヴァントを強制的に操れるのはたったの三回
令呪を全て失ったら　僕はこいつを制御できなくなる
I won't be able to control him if I use up all my Command Spells.
I have no complaints as long as I get the Grail.
聖杯さえ手に入るなら　それで文句はない
Do whatever you want afterwards-
そのあとでお前が何をしようと知らない
ああ　もう　聖杯はちゃんと余が手に入れてやる
Yes, okay! I'll acquire the Grail for you.
You seem confident.
ずいぶん自信があるみたいだけど  お前　何か勝算はあるのか
What makes you think you can win?
Are you saying you wish to see my power?
つまり　貴様は余の力が見たいと
O-Of course!
と　当然だろう
You need to prove that I can rely on you!
お前を信用していいのかどうか　証明してもらわないとな
I am Iskandar, King of Conquerors!
征服王イスカンダルがこの一斬にて覇権を問う
With the swing of my sword, I declare my supremacy!
King Gordias made this very offering to Zeus.
ゴルディアス王がゼウス神に捧げた供物でな
Its renown must be the source of my designation as Rider.
余がライダーの座に据えられたのも　きっとこいつの評判のせいであろう
If you want the Grail, then go find me another Heroic Spirit or two!
聖杯が欲しいなら
さっさと英霊の一人や二人　居場所を突き止めて見せんかい
Until then, I shall entertain myself with these maps.
それまでは　地図でも眺めて無聊の慰めとするが
No problems with that?
まあ　文句はあるまい
Okay! I won't lose today!
よーし　今日こそは絶対に負けないからね
お　見つけた
Found one.
No way! Where?!
嘘　どこどこ
I'm pretty sure I didn't miss any!
わたし見落としたりしてないのに
That's today's first walnut bud.
今日一個目のくるみの冬芽だ
One point for me.
先取点ね
I... I won't lose!
負けないもん
Found one!
あ　あった
I found one, too!
イリヤも一個みーつけた
父さんも二個目を見つけたぞ
But I already found two.
That's not a walnut branch.
あの枝　くるみじゃないよ
No, Ilya. That's called a wingnut.
いやいや　イリヤ
あの枝はサワグルミといってたな
くるみの仲間なんだよ
It's similar to a walnut.
That makes it a walnut bud, too.
だからあれも　くるみの冬芽だ
ずるーい　ずるい　ずるい　ずるい
No fair!
No fair! No fair!
切嗣ずーっとズルしてた
You've been cheating this whole time, Kiritsugu!
But Daddy has no chance of winning otherwise.
だってな　こうでもしないと父さん勝ち目ないし
I won't play with you if you keep cheating!
そういうずるいことばっかりやってたら  もう切嗣と遊んであげないんだから
そりゃ困る　ごめんごめん　謝るよ
Oh, no! I'm sorry! I apologize.
Do you promise not to cheat anymore?
もうずるしないって約束する
I promise.
Very well.
よろしい　なら　また勝負してあげる
I accept your challenge.
チャンピオンはいつでも挑戦を受けるのだ
A champion takes on all challengers!
Indeed. I am honored...
はい　光栄であります
...my princess!
お姫様
I'm so high up!
高い　高い
What are you looking at, Saber?
何を見てるの　セイバー
Your daughter and Kiritsugu are playing in the woods outside.
外の森で　ご息女と切嗣が戯れていたもので
Surprised?
意外だった
I was under the impression that my Master was colder than that.
私のマスターはもっと冷酷な人物だという印象があったので
Well, I can see why you might think so.
まあ　それは無理もないわよね
If that is Kiritsugu's true self...
あれが切嗣の素顔だというのなら
I must have gravely offended him.
私はマスターからよほど不興を買ったのでしょうね
Irisviel! This isn't funny!
アイリスフィール　何も笑うことはないでしょう
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさいね　召喚されたときのこと　まだ気にしてるのかなと思って
I was wondering if what happened during your summoning still bothered you.
It does, a little.
いささか
It's true that I passed myself as a man,
確かに私は男として振る舞っていましたか
but there was no need for both of you to be so taken aback.
何も二人揃ってあれほど驚くこともないでしよう
Well, we just couldn't help it.
そうは言ってもね　仕方がないのよ
Your legend... King Arthur's legend... is simply too famous.
あなたのアーサー王の伝説はあまりに有名なんだもの
Do you suppose Kiritsugu thinks light of my ability because I'm a woman?
切嗣には　私の正体が女であったが故に　侮られているのでしょうか
それはないわ
Not at all.
でも
But...
Indeed, there's another reason why he's upset.
そうね
彼が腹を立てているとするなら
それは別の理由でしょうね
Another?
別の
He's probably upset at the people who were around you.
多分あの人は あなたを囲んでいた人たちに対して腹を立てているのね
People cruel enough to force the role of a king on a young girl.
小さな女の子に「王」という役目を押しつけて良しとした残酷な人たちに
It was inevitable.
それは是非もないことでした
I had resolved myself to that fate
when I drew the sword from the stone.
岩の剣を抜く時から　私も覚悟を決めていた
そんな風にあなたが運命を受け入れてしまったのが 尚のこと腹立たしいのよ
The fact that you accepted your fate upsets him all the more.
He forgets his place, then.
それは出過ぎた感傷だ
He does not have the right to question decisions made by those of my time, including myself.
私の時代の　私を含めた人間たちの判断について
そこまでとやかく言われる筋合いはない
That's why he isn't saying anything.
だから黙ってるのよ　あの人は
Emiya Kiritsugu and the Hero Arturia will never see eye to eye.
衛宮切嗣とアルトリアという英雄とでは
どうあっても相容れないと
Indeed, he's given up on trying.
そう諦めてしまっているのね
He wants to use the Grail's power to save the world.
聖杯の力によって世界を救済したい
Is that not Kiritsugu's and your common wish?
それがあなたと切嗣の願いてしたね
Yes, but I'm merely repeating what he said.
ええ　私のは　あの人の受け売りでしかないけれど
私が聖杯に託す願いもまた同じです
My own desire for the Grail is the same.
I wish to save Britain, since I was unable to do so before.
この手で護りきれなかったブリテンを 私は何としても救済したい
I think what you and Kiritsugu seek is right.
あなたと切嗣が目指すものは正しいと思います
It is something to be proud of.
誇って良い道だと
Our next match won't be until you come home from Japan, right?
That's right.
How long will your work keep you and Mommy away?
When will you be back?
I'll be back in about two weeks.
Mommy won't be back for quite a while, though.
Yeah, Mommy told me already.
She said she'll be away for a long time.
She said that even if we can't see each other for a long time, she'd always be by my side.
So she told me I shouldn't feel lonely,
last night before I went to bed.
I'm gonna be together with Mommy forever and ever!
I see.
Listen, Ilya.
Kiritsugu?
Can you wait for me?
Even if you're lonely, can you hold on until I come home?
Yeah!
I promise you, then.
I'll come home straight away.
Fill, fill, fill 'er up, fill...
みったせー   みったせー   みったして   みったせー
Repeat four times...
繰り返すつどに四度
Wait, was it five times?
あれ  五度
Um, destroy each when filled...
えーと ただ満たされるトキを破却する だよなあ
...or something?
みったせー  みったせー  みったして  みったして  みったせと
Fill, fill, fill, fill, fill.
はい 今度こそ五度ね
All right, that makes five times!
オーケイ
Okay.
At all three murder scenes, a mysterious pentagram drawn with the victims' blood was found.
これまで起こった三件の殺害現場すべてに
被害者の血で描かれた魔法陣と思われる謎の図柄が残されていたことが
At all the locations
of the
bizarre serial killin
gs in Fuyuki City,
mysterious pen
tagram
s have been dra
wn in blood.
Maybe I went a little too far.
ちょっと 羽目を外し過ぎちゃったかもな
描かれた 魔法陣は一体何を
At all the locations of
mysterious pentagrams
the bizarre serial killings in Fuyuki City,
have
been drawn in blood.
The purpose of the pentagrams remains unclear.
At all the locations of
mysterious pentagrams
the bizarre serial killings in Fuyuki City,
have
been drawn in blood.
At all the locations of
mysterious pentagrams
the bizarre serial killings in Fuyuki City,
At all the locations of
mysterious pentagrams
the bizarre serial killings in Fuyuki City,
have
been drawn in blood.
the bizarre serial killings in Fuyuki City,
mysterious pentagrams
have
the bizarre serial killings in Fuyuki City,
been drawn in blood.
本日は犯罪心理に詳しい
Today, we've invited a specialist in criminal psychology-
Do you think demons exist, kiddo?
悪魔って本当にいると思うかい 坊や
All the papers and magazines call me a demon.
新聞や雑誌だとさ
よくオレのこと悪魔呼ばわりしたりするんだよね
But wouldn't that be kinda rude if demons really did exist?
でもそれって
もし本物の悪魔がいたりしたら
ちょっとばかり失礼な話だよね
You've gotta be clear about these things.
そこんとこ スッキリしなくてさあ
チワッス 雨生龍之介は悪魔であります
Sup! I'm Uryuu Ryuunosuke, and I'm a demon!
I dunno if that's how I should be introducing myself.
なんて名乗っちゃっていいもんかどうか
So like, I found this.
そしたら こんな物見つけちゃってさ
うちの土蔵にあった古文書みたいなやつなんだけどさ
It's some old book I found in the storehouse.
It looks like my ancestors were researching how to summon demons.
どうも うちのご先祖様悪魔を呼び出す研究をしてたみたいなんだよね
そしたらさ 本物の悪魔がいるのか確かめるしかないじゃん
So like, I've gotta find out if demons really do exist!
でもね  万が一本当に悪魔とかが出てきちゃったらさ
But y'know...
If a demon really did come out, it'd be pretty dumb to just chat with it and have nothing to offer him.
何の準備もなくて茶飲み話だけってのもマヌケな話じゃん
だからね 坊や
So, kiddo...
もし悪魔サンがお出まししたら
If a demon really does show up...
Mind if we let it kill you?
ひとつ殺されてみてくれない
I wonder what it's like, being killed by a demon!
悪魔に殺されるのって  どんなだろうねえ
貴重な体験だ
Not many people get to experience that- Ow!
あ　痛っ
What's this?
何だ  これ
問おう
I ask you.
You, who calls me and seeks me...
我を呼び 我を求め
キャスターの座を依り代に現界せしめた召喚者
Summoner who manifests me under the class of Caster...
I ask your name.
貴殿の名をここに問う
Yes...
其は 何者なるや
Who are you?
Uh...
えと  えと　雨生龍之介っす
I'm Uryuu Ryuunosuke.
I'm currently unemployed, and I like killing people, pretty much.
職業フリーター
趣味は人殺し全般
子供とか若い女とか好きです
Especially kids and young women.
宣しい　契約は成立しました
Very well. The contract is made.
I desire the Grail, as do you.
貴殿の求める聖杯は 私もまた悲願とするところ
かの楽園の釜は必ずや 我らの手にするところとなるでしょう
The vessel of paradise shall belong to us.
せい  はい
The Gra... What?
Anyway, how about a sacrifice?
まあ とりあえず お近づきにご一献どうですか
Wanna eat that kid?
あれ  食べない
あ すげえ  それ人間の皮でしょう
Whoa! That's human skin, right?
Cthulhu fhtagn.
Cthulhu Fhtagn
Don't be scared, boy.
怖がらなくていいんだよ 坊や
Can you stand?
立てるかい
Now, boy, you can leave the room through that door.
さあ  坊や
あそこの扉から部屋の外に出られる
ひとりで行けるね
You can go by yourself, right?
Yeah.
Hey, what's wrong with you?!
なあ  ちょっと
Some forms of terror are fresher than others.
恐怖というものには鮮度があります
The more intense the fear, the more the emotions die.
怯えれば怯えるほどに　感情とは死んでいくものなのです
Terror, in its truest sense, is not a static state, but a dynamic one.
真の意味での恐怖とは
静的な状態ではなく 変化の動態
It is the moment when hope turns to despair.
希望が絶望へと切り替わる その瞬間のことを言う
Did you enjoy that?
如何でしたか
The taste of fresh terror and death?
瑞々しく新鮮な恐怖と死の味は
Cool! You're awesome!
クール 最高だ
You're so cool, man!
超クールだよ　アンタ
Okay!
オーケイだ
聖杯だか何だか知らないが
I don't know about this Grail crap,
but I'm following you from now on!
とにかくオレはアンタに付いていく
さあ  殺そう
Kill more!
もっともっとクールな殺しっぷりでオレを魅せてくれ
Show me even cooler ways to kill people!
Ryuunosuke, wasn't it?
リュウノスケといいましたか
貴殿のような理解あるマスターを得られたのは幸先がいい
How fortunate of me to be blessed with an understanding Master like yourself.
これはいよいよ 我が悲願の達成に期待が持てそうです
It feels like my dream is almost within my grasp.
Oh, yeah. I didn't get your name.
あ そういえば
オレまだアンタの名前聞いてない
名前ですか
My name?
そうですね  この時代で通りの良い呼び名とえば
Let me see. In this era, I would probably be known as...
I think I'll take the name of Bluebeard for now.
では  ひとまず『青髭』とでも名乗っておきましょうか
The Church has just informed me that the seventh Servant, Caster, has appeared.
聖堂教会から
七体目のサーヴァント キャスターが現界したとの連絡があった
最後のサーヴァントが召喚されましたか
The final Servant has been summoned? Then it is time.
ではいよいよ
Indeed.
そういうことだ
You are to head immediately for the Tohsaka household.
早速だが お前にはこれから 遠坂邸へ向かってもらう
And when I arrive?
と申しますと
お前ならば
The house's powerful magic fields should be child's play to you.
あの遠坂邸の要塞のような魔術結界も
恐るるに足りぬだろう
宣しいのですか
Are you sure?
遠坂時臣とは同盟関係と聞いておりましたが
I believe you're supposed to be allied with Tohsaka Tokiomi.
それは考慮しなくていい
Don't worry about that.
Even if you end up having to fight Archer, there is no need to fear.
例えアーチャーと対決する羽目になろうとも
恐れる必要はない
三大騎士クラスのアーチャーを恐れる必要はないと仰るとは
No need to fear Archer, one of the three great knight classes?
任せたぞ
I'm counting on you.
You are to promptly kill Tohsaka Tokiomi.
すみやかに遠坂時臣を抹殺しろ
たわいない
This is too easy.
Little worm crawling on the ground.
地を這う虫ケラ風情が
誰の許しを得て面を上げる
Who gave you permission to look up?
He said...
あれを 恐れることはない だと
I didn't need...
...to fear him?!
You are not worthy to gaze upon me.
貴様は我を見るに能わぬ
A worm should just continue staring at the ground...
虫ケラは虫ケラらしく 地だけを眺めながら
死ね
...as it dies.
Episode 2
False Opening
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
At last, it is time for the 4th Holy Grail War to start.
いよいよ始まるぞ 第四次聖杯戦争が
度し難たいほどに醜悪だ
It's unspeakably ugly.
預けておいたやつは  何処だ
Where is the thing I left with you?
盛り上がってきたはいい
This will be fun!
よくぞきた
Welcome.
この私に勝利を
Bring me victory!
はい  必ずや
Yes, without fail.
Next Episode
Land of Winter Trees